

# Profile

Passionate and Hardworking self learn't and who is currently a student studying at Monash university, doing a full stack developer course i really love learning technologies. My best strengths be API'S, researching, and working on front-end Development for now and working in a team. My weakness would be knowledge on back-end. I have been studying and self learning doing courses on udemy for the past two years. I would like to join your company i reckon i would be a great candidate specially with my skill-set.

# Employment History

Junior Eletrcian at Peter Brown, Melbourne

November 2018 — July 2019

Responsibilities: Measuring and laying out points, installing air

conditions, and laboring.

Noni's Pizza at Yasemin Simmons - General Manager, Melbourne

January 2013 — December 2015

Responsibilities: Taking Orders, Making Pizza's, and Cleaning

## Education

chisholm institute, Melbourne

Year 12 VCE

Subjects: Bushiness Management, Method Maths, Chemistry, Further Maths.

## Courses

full stack developer, Monash university

November 2022 — April 2023

The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert!, udemy

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp, udemy

### **Details**

melbourne Australia 0452 144 565

kayhanturk90@live.com

#### Links

Github TravelBug-App Universal-Forcast Quizz-game

#### **Skills**

**Bootstrap** 

HTML & CSS

Node.js

Git

**CSS** 

**HTML** 

JavaScript

Jquery

Bulma

#### **Hobbies**

MMA, Snorkelling, Gaming, Snowboarding, swimming.

# Languages

Turkish